John H. Cornehlsen Papers 5730
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
John H. Cornehlsen Papers
1920-1983
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Cornehlsen, John H.
5730
59.5 cubic feet
56 linear ft.
Records (documents).
This collection consists of psychological profiles of individuals in corporate middle-management positions, samples of tests that could be used to create those profiles, as well as samples of other psychological and personality tests, and office files from Dr. Cornehlsen's career as a consulting psychologist and a psychology professor.
3338515
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, April 02, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, April 18, 2017
Biographical / Historical
Dr. John Henry Cornehlsen, Jr. was an industrial psychologist working mainly in the mid-twentieth century. Dr. Cornehlsen was born in New York City on December 27, 1906. He graduated from Dartmouth College in 1929, earned his Master's degree from Harvard University in 1938, and received his Ph.D. from Stanford University in 1942.
He worked as a consulting psychologist for various firms, including his own, and for the Department of Defense. In his consulting he specialized in executive selection and appraisal; career development and counseling; personnel selection and guidance. During the Second World War Dr. Cornehlsen was involved with officer selection in the Bureau of Naval Personnel.
In addition to his consulting work he taught psychology at St. Lawrence College, Stanford University, San Francisco State College, New York University, and C. W. Post College. The courses taught by Dr. Cornehlsen at C. W. Post included: Child Psychology, Adolescent Psychology, Social Psychology, Industrial Psychology, Abnormal Psychology, Behavior Management in the Classroom, and Executive Leadership and Supervision.
Dr. Cornehlsen died on February 1, 1998.
Scope and Contents
The John H. Cornehlsen Papers consists of three series: Psychological Profiles, Sample Tests, and Office Files. The psychological profiles are two-thirds of the collection, consisting of over 2,000 profiles of middle managers done by Dr. Cornehlsen for several major corporations to aid in hiring or promotion decisions. Also included are psychological profiles done for individuals wanting to position themselves better in the job market. They usually consist of handwritten interview notes, a type assessment of the individual's psychological profile, and a battery of personality and cognitive tests. Typically the battery of tests includes: a personality inventory, a temperament survey, a study of values, an interest profile, and Dr. Cornehlsen's own sentence completion test. Depending on the profile, other tests may be included, while some of the aforementioned may be absent. The profiles are grouped by company then alphabetically within the company by last name. The tests done for individuals themselves are arranged separately in alphabetical order by last name. For reasons of privacy the folder titles do not include either the name of the company the profile was done for, or the name of the individual profiled. Most of these profiles were done in the late 1950s and early 1960s, with most of the individuals being men in their 40s and 50s.
The second series, Sample Tests, consists of blank samples for over 250 different tests. Not all samples included are complete, some consist only of the manual of directions or only of the blank question form. The samples are arranged alphabetically by title or by publisher, then title, where appropriate. The tests included in this sample set are designed to measure intelligence, cognitive ability, personality, personal preferences, language ability, math ability, sales ability, clerical ability, judgment, employee attitude, vocational interest, art and music appreciation, and many other aspects of a person's psychological/personality makeup.
The third series, Office Files, consists of files pertaining to Dr. Cornehlsen's work as a consulting psychologist or psychology professor. This includes memos, correspondence, and other files from Mahler and Associates; correspondence, reports, resumes, and other files from Richardson, Bellows, Henry, and Company; correspondence, notes, and other material for creating and updating a "Career Guidance" pamphlet for the New York Life Insurance Company; and correspondence from Cornehlsen and Associates. There is also material from several courses Dr. Cornehlsen taught, mostly at C. W. Post College. The course files consist of notes, syllabi, bibliographies, exams, and course evaluation forms filled out by students. A few article reprints, mostly concerning executive training and evaluation are also a part of this section, as are a few folders of Dr. Cornehlsen's personal correspondence and papers.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3051: Albert Martin Papers 5227: Edward Northup Hay Papers 6255: Richard Sears Barrett Papers
Arrangement
Series I: Psychological Profiles
Sub-Series A: Profiles done for Companies Sub-Series B: Profiles done for Individuals
Series II: Sample Tests
Sub-Series A: Blank Samples Sub-Series B: Completed Tests and Other Forms
Series III: Office Files
Sub-Series A: Consulting Sub-Series B: Teaching Sub-Series C: Personal
Psychology, Industrial -- United States; Cornehlsen, John Henry Jr., 1906-1998; Cornehlsen and Associates; Curtiss-Wright Corporation; Franklin National Bank; General Electric; James C. Sinnigen & Co.; Mahler and Associates; Monsanto; New York Life Insurance Company; Psychological Corporation; Richardson, Bellows, Henry, and Company; Science Research Associates (SRA); Telecomputing Corporation; U.S. Rubber
3338515
- Series I: Psychological Profiles
  - Sub-Series A: Profiles done for Companies
    - Company A: Ab, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Scope and Contents
      Code: 10A
    - Company A: Ab, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Company A: Ab, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Code: 13A
    - Company A: Ac, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Code: 27A
    - Company A: Ac, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Code: 4A
    - Company A: Ad, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Code: 3A
    - Company A: Ad, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Code: 9A
    - Company A: Ad, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Company A: Ag, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      Code: 12A
    - Company A: Ag, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      Code: 11A
    - Company A: Ah, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      Code: 5A
    - Company A: Ah, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      Code: 28A
    - Company A: Ai, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Company A: Al, 1956-1958 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      Code: 26A
    - Company A: Al, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 15)
      Code: 22A
    - Company A: Al, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 16)
      Code: 8A
    - Company A: Al, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Company A: Al, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 18)
      Code: 24A
    - Company A: Al, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 19)
      Code: 6A
    - Company A: An, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 20)
      Code: 7A
    - Company A: An, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 21)
      Code: 21A
    - Company A: Ar, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 22)
      Code: 2A
    - Company A: Ar, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 23)
      Code: 20A
    - Company A: Ar, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 24)
      Code: 25A
    - Company A: Ar, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 25)
      Code: 14A
    - Company A: Ar, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 26)
      Code: 23A
    - Company A: Ba, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 27)
      Code: 58B
    - Company A: Ba, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 27)
      Code: 3B
    - Company A: Ba, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 29)
      Code: 52B
    - Company A: Ba, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 30)
      Code: 51B
    - Company A: Ba, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 31)
      Code: 53B
    - Company A: Ba, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 32)
      Code: 23B
    - Company A: Ba, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 33)
      Code: 54B
    - Company A: Ba, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Company A: Ba, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 35)
      Code: 61B
    - Company A: Ba, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 36)
      Code: 24B
    - Company A: Ba, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 37)
      Code: 71B
    - Company A: Ba, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 38)
      Code: 9B
    - Company A: Ba, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 39)
      Code: 55B
    - Company A: Ba, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 40)
      Code: 56B
    - Company A: Be, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 41)
      Code: 41B
    - Company A: Be, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 42)
      Code: 29B
    - Company A: Be, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 43)
      Code: 72B
    - Company A: Be, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 44)
      Code: 57B
    - Company A: Be, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 45)
      Code: 25B
    - Company A: Be, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 46)
      Code: 36B
    - Company A: Be, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Company A: Be, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 48)
      Code: 14B
    - Company A: Be, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 49)
      Code: 4B
    - Company A: Be, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 50)
      Code: 15B
    - Company A: Be, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 51)
      Code: 73B
    - Company A: Be, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 52)
      Code: 27B
    - Company A: Be, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 53)
      Code: 26B
    - Company A: Be, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 54)
      Code: 44B
    - Company A: Be, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 55)
      Code: 1B
    - Company A: Be, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 56)
      Code: 43B
    - Company A: Be, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 57)
      Code: 67B
    - Company A: Be, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 58)
      Code: 28B
    - Company A: Be, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 59)
      Code: 50B
    - Company A: Bh, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Code: 62B
    - Company A: Bi, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Code: 5B
    - Company A: Bi, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Code: 40B
    - Company A: Bi, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      Code: 74B
    - Company A: Bi, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      Code: 30B
    - Company A: Bi, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      Code: 49B
    - Company A: Bi, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      Code: 6B
    - Company A: Bi, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Code: 48B
    - Company A: Bj, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Company A: Bj, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Company A: Bl, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      Code: 63B
    - Company A: Bl, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      Code: 8B
    - Company A: Bl, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      Code: 10B
    - Company A: Bl, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      Code: 11B
    - Company A: Bl, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      Code: 31B
    - Company A: Bo, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 16)
      Code: 65B
    - Company A: Bo, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Company A: Bo, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Company A: Bo, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      Code: 12B
    - Company A: Bo, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 20)
      Code: 69B
    - Company A: Bo, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Company A: Bo, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      Code: 13B
    - Company A: Br, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      Code: 16B
    - Company A: Br, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Company A: Br, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      Code: 46B
    - Company A: Br, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      Code: 39B
    - Company A: Br, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 27)
      Code: 47B
    - Company A: Br, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 28)
      Code: 42B
    - Company A: Br, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 29)
      Code: 38B
    - Company A: Br, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Company A: Br, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 31)
      Code: 59B
    - Company A: Br, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 32)
      Code: 66B
    - Company A: Br, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 33)
      Code: 19B
    - Company A: Br, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 34)
      Code: 17B
    - Company A: Br, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 35)
      Code: 64B
    - Company A: Br, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 36)
      Code: 18B
    - Company A: Br, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 37)
      Code: 33B
    - Company A: Br, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Company A: Br, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 39)
      Code: 21B
    - Company A: Br, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 40)
      Code: 45B
    - Company A: Br, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 41)
      Code: 60B
    - Company A: Br, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 42)
      Code: 2B
    - Company A: Br, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 43)
      Code: 75B
    - Company A: Br, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 44)
      Code: 20B
    - Company A: Bu, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 45)
      Code: 22B
    - Company A: Bu, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 46)
      Code: 32B
    - Company A: Bu, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 47)
      Code: 34B
    - Company A: Bu, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 48)
      Code: 70B
    - Company A: Bu, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 49)
      Code: 37B
    - Company A: Bu, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 50)
      Code: 35B
    - Company A: Bu, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 51)
      Code: 68B
    - Company A: By, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Company A: Ca, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 53)
      Code: 1C
    - Company A: Ca, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 54)
      Code: 11C
    - Company A: Ca, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 55)
      Code: 12C
    - Company A: Ca, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 56)
      Code: 30C
    - Company A: Ca, 1957-1958 (Box 2, Folder 57)
      Code: 43C
    - Company A: Ca, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Code: 2C
    - Company A: Ca, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      Code: 23C
    - Company A: Ca, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Code: 24C
    - Company A: Ca, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      Code: 41C
    - Company A: Ca, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      Code: 14C
    - Company A: Ca, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      Code: 32C
    - Company A: Ca, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      Code: 45C
    - Company A: Ca, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      Code: 13C
    - Company A: Ca, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      Code: 46C
    - Company A: Ca, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Code: 44C
    - Company A: Ce, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      Code: 31C
    - Company A: Ch, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      Code: 15C
    - Company A: Ch, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      Code: 16C
    - Company A: Ch, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Code: 42C
    - Company A: Ch, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      Code: 21C
    - Company A: Ch, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Company A: Cl, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      Code: 17C
    - Company A: Cl, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      Code: 40C
    - Company A: Cl, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      Code: 4C
    - Company A: Co, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      Code: 28C
    - Company A: Co, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 21)
      Code: 3C
    - Company A: Co, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Company A: Co, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      Code: 33C
    - Company A: Co, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      Code: 5C
    - Company A: Co, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 25)
      Code: 38C
    - Company A: Co, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Company A: Co, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 27)
      Code: 6C
    - Company A: Co, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 28)
      Code: 19C
    - Company A: Co, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 29)
      Code: 35C
    - Company A: Co, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 30)
      Code: 20C
    - Company A: Co, 1956-1957 (Box 3, Folder 31)
      Code: 27C
    - Company A: Co, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 32)
      Code: 34C
    - Company A: Co, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 33)
      Code: 7C
    - Company A: Co, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 34)
      Code: 25C
    - Company A: Co, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 35)
      Code: 39C
    - Company A: Cr, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 36)
      Code: 8C
    - Company A: Cr, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 37)
      Code: 36C
    - Company A: Cr, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 38)
      Code: 29C
    - Company A: Cr, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 39)
      Code: 37C
    - Company A: Cu, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Company A: Cu, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 41)
      Code: 9C
    - Company A: Cu, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 42)
      Code: 22C
    - Company A: Cu, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 43)
      Code: 10C
    - Company A: Da, 1958-1962 (Box 3, Folder 44)
      Code: 38D
    - Company A: Da, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 45)
      Code: 4D
    - Company A: Da, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 46)
      Code: 13D
    - Company A: Da, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 47)
      Code: 26D
    - Company A: Da, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Company A: Da, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 49)
      Code: 25D
    - Company A: Da, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 50)
      Code: 5D
    - Company A: Da, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 51)
      Code: 6D
    - Company A: Da, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 52)
      Code: 19D
    - Company A: Da, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 53)
      Code: 28D
    - Company A: Da, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 54)
      Code: 14D
    - Company A: Da, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 55)
      Code: 29D
    - Company A: Da, 1961-1962 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Company A: Da, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 57)
      Code: 18D
    - Company A: De, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 58)
      Code: 2D
    - Company A: De, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 59)
      Code: 15D
    - Company A: De, 196 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Company A: De, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 61)
      Code: 32D
    - Company A: De, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Code: 7D
    - Company A: De, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      Code: 33D
    - Company A: De, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      Code: 43D
    - Company A: De, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      Code: 8D
    - Company A: De, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Code: 34D
    - Company A: De, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      Code: 27D
    - Company A: De, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Company A: De, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      Code: 37D
    - Company A: De, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Company A: De, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      Code: 41D
    - Company A: Di, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Company A: Di, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      Code: 9D
    - Company A: Di, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      Code: 11D
    - Company A: Do, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      Code: 3D
    - Company A: Do, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      Code: 80
    - Company A: Do, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Company A: Do, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 17)
      Code: 17D
    - Company A: Do, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 18)
      Code: 42D
    - Company A: Do, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Company A: Do, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Company A: Do, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 21)
      Code: 40D
    - Company A: Do, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 22)
      Code: 30D
    - Company A: Do, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 23)
      Code: 20D
    - Company A: Do, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Company A: Dr, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 25)
      Code: 24D
    - Company A: Dr, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 26)
      Code: 39D
    - Company A: Dr, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 27)
      Code: 36D
    - Company A: Du, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Company A: Du, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 29)
      Code: 31D
    - Company A: Du, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 30)
      Code: 1D
    - Company A: Du, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 31)
      Code: 21D
    - Company A: Du, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 32)
      Code: 35D
    - Company A: Du, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 33)
      Code: 23D
    - Company A: Du, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 34)
      Code: 12D
    - Company A: Dw, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 35)
      Code: 22D
    - Company A: Ea, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 36)
      Code: 1E
    - Company A: Ed, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 37)
      Code: 8E
    - Company A: Eh, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 38)
      Code: 4E
    - Company A: Eh, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 39)
      Code: 6E
    - Company A: Ek, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 40)
      Code: 13E
    - Company A: El, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 41)
      Code: 5E
    - Company A: El, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Company A: El, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 43)
      Code: 2E
    - Company A: El, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 44)
      Code: 10E
    - Company A: En, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 45)
      Code: 11E
    - Company A: Er, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 46)
      Code: 3E
    - Company A: Er, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 47)
      Code: 7E
    - Company A: Eu, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 48)
      Code: 14E
    - Company A: Ez, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 49)
      Code: 12E
    - Company A: Fa, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 50)
      Code: 8F
    - Company A: Fe, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 51)
      Code: 22F
    - Company A: Fe, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 52)
      Code: 14F
    - Company A: Fe, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 53)
      Code: 20F
    - Company A: Fe, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 54)
      Code: 23F
    - Company A: Fe, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Company A: Fe, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 56)
      Code:3F
    - Company A: Fe, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 57)
      Code: 9F
    - Company A: Fe, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 58)
      Code: 24F
    - Company A: Fi, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      Code: 4F
    - Company A: Fi, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      Code: 16F
    - Company A: Fi, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Code: 25F
    - Company A: Fi, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Company A: Fi, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Company A: Fl, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Company A: Fl, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      Code: 15F
    - Company A: Fl, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      Code: 5F
    - Company A: Fo, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      Code: 11F
    - Company A: Fo, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      Code: 26F
    - Company A: Fo, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      Code: 13F
    - Company A: Fr, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      Code: 18F
    - Company A: Fr, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      Code: 6F
    - Company A: Fr, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      Code: 12G
    - Company A: Fr, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      Code: 27F
    - Company A: Fr, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      Code: 19F
    - Company A: Fr, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      Code: 7F
    - Company A: Fo, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      Code: 10F
    - Company A: Fu, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 19)
      Code: 12F
    - Company A: Fu, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 20)
      Code: 1F
    - Company A: Fu, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      Code: 2F
    - Company A: Ga, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 22)
      Code: 18G
    - Company A: Ge, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 23)
      Code: 20G
    - Company A: Ge, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Company A: Ge, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 25)
      Code: 19G
    - Company A: Gi, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Company A: Gi, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 27)
      Code: 22G
    - Company A: Gi, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 28)
      Code: 5G
    - Company A: Gi, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Company A: Go, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 30)
      Code: 13G
    - Company A: Go, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 31)
      Code: 6G
    - Company A: Go, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 32)
      Code: 14G
    - Company A: Go, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Company A: Go, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Company A: Gr, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Company A: Gr, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 36)
      Code: 11G
    - Company A: Gr, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 37)
      Code: 15G
    - Company A: Gr, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 38)
      Code: 4G
    - Company A: Gr, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 39)
      Code: 23G
    - Company A: Gr, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 40)
      Code: 7G
    - Company A: Gr, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 41)
      Code: 26G
    - Company A: Gr, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Company A: Gr, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 43)
      Code: 8G
    - Company A: Gr, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 44)
      Code: 24G
    - Company A: Gr, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 45)
      Code: 21G
    - Company A: Gr, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 46)
      Code: 9G
    - Company A: Gu, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 47)
      Code: 3G
    - Company A: Gu, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 48)
      Code: 10G
    - Company A: Gu, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 49)
      Code: 17G
    - Company A: Gu, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 50)
      Code: 25G
    - Company A: Ha, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 51)
      Code: 10H
    - Company A: Ha, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 52)
      Code: 39H
    - Company A: Ha, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 53)
      Code: 52H
    - Company A: Ha, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 54)
      Code: 21H
    - Company A: Ha, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 55)
      Code: 21F
    - Company A: Ha, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 56)
      Code: 6H
    - Company A: Ha, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Company A: Ha, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      Code: 20H
    - Company A: Ha, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      Code: 37H
    - Company A: Ha, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      Code: 43H
    - Company A: Ha, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Company A: Ha, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      Code: 55H
    - Company A: Ha, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      Code: 40H
    - Company A: Ha, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      Code: 45H
    - Company A: Ha, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      Code: 46H
    - Company A: Ha, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      Code: 11H
    - Company A: Ha, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      Code: 24H
    - Company A: Ha, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Company A: Ha, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      Code: 7H
    - Company A: Ha, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 14)